Hey y'all, Greg here aboard the veteran boat attached to the Global Samud Flotilla.
Our boat was assailed by a quadcopter and they dropped a little popper on deck.
Another couple boats experienced that as well.
And also our VHF radio was hijacked by adversarial comms and they started playing ABBA.
So this is the initiation of the psychological operations that we had mentioned previously.
They're beginning off the coast of Crete.
Luckily we have live stream footage that gets stored in a backup.
Unfortunately this was out of frame, but you see we noticed the quadcopter drone run back.
Yeah, somewhat startling.
Yeah, so I'm going to park my head here so I cover it up, whichever VHF channel we use, but we've been dealing with this all night.
Yeah, so that was ABBA. ABBA's from Sweden.
Obviously their weird obsession with Greta Thunberg being on the flotilla may have something to do with it.
But we're probably going to be expecting this every night going forward, you know, to just break everyone down psychologically.
This is what they are. There's no injuries. Everyone's fine.
These are just psychological operations.
And they're probably going to increase in intensity and frequency from here on out every time the sun sets.
So we appreciate your attention to this matter.
Pressure your governments, please, to protect the flotilla and we will not be deterred.
So we're just going to keep on sailing and they're going to keep doing what they're going to keep doing and history will be our judge.